{
    "id": "chishima",
    "name": "Chishima Foundation for Creative Osaka",
    "yomi": "おおさか創造千島財団",
    "text": [
        "北加賀屋を拠点に、大阪やその周辺で活動するアーティスト、クリエイター、また彼らを支える人たちの活動を支援する事業を行っています。"
    ],
    "link": [
        {
            "a": "Website",
            "href": "https://chishima-foundation.com/"
        }
    ],
    "questions": [
        {
            "id": "Q1",
            "question": "You wear your shoes first from",
            "jp": "靴を履くのは",
            "yes": "right",
            "left": "右から",
            "no": "left",
            "right": "左から"
        },
        {
            "id": "Q2",
            "question": "Did you take train to get here today?",
            "jp": "今日は電車に乗ってきた",
            "yes": "yes",
            "left": "はい",
            "no": "no",
            "right": "いいえ"
        },
        {
            "id": "Q3",
            "question": "Which do you think is more interesting if they are colored?",
            "jp": "色がついていたらおもしろいと思うのは",
            "yes": "rain",
            "left": "雨",
            "no": "tear",
            "right": "涙"
        },
        {
            "id": "Q4",
            "question": "Do you want to meet yourself in 20 years?",
            "jp": "20年後の自分に会いたいと思いますか？",
            "yes": "yes",
            "left": "はい",
            "no": "no",
            "right": "いいえ"
        },
        {
            "id": "Q5",
            "question": "For camping you'd go to",
            "jp": "キャンプをするなら",
            "yes": "the mountain",
            "left": "山",
            "no": "the beach",
            "right": "海"
        },
        {
            "id": "Q6",
            "question": "You prefer Hotcake to pancake?",
            "jp": "パンケーキよりホットケーキが好きだ",
            "yes": "yes",
            "left": "はい",
            "no": "no",
            "right": "いいえ"
        },
        {
            "id": "Q7",
            "question": "Tomato should be eaten with salt",
            "jp": "トマトに塩は",
            "yes": "yes",
            "left": "いる",
            "no": "no",
            "right": "いらない"
        },
        {
            "id": "Q8",
            "question": "Do you often go to 100yen shop?",
            "jp": "100均にはよく行きますか",
            "yes": "yes",
            "left": "はい",
            "no": "no",
            "right": "いいえ"
        },
        {
            "id": "Q9",
            "question": "Which do you want it wider in your room?",
            "jp": "ワンルームマンションで広かったらうれしいのは",
            "yes": "kitchen",
            "left": "キッチン",
            "no": "balcony",
            "right": "ベランダ"
        },
        {
            "id": "Q10",
            "question": "Which is round?",
            "jp": "丸いのはどっち",
            "yes": "a ballon",
            "left": "ふうせん",
            "no": "a cat",
            "right": "ねこ"
        }
    ]
}